mplstudios.com 2018-12-19

# MPL Studios

By visiting mplstudios.com or sweet-lilya.com, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy please contact us by email at webmaster [@] mplstudios.com

**What kind of information do you collect?**  
When you join the membership portion of our web site you are asked to provide your name, address, e-mail, and credit card number. This information is collected and processed using SSL encryption, provided by a third party payment processor. When users request pages from our web server, our server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses, location, browser type, login dates and time, and download history. We also collect information regarding your use of our site through ‘cookies’. We use cookies to improve the quality of your browsing experience, for storing your site preferences, and tracking user trends, such as how people surf the site. These cookies do not contain any private information and cannot be traced back to you as a user in any way. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account.

**How do you use my information?**  
We use your information solely to process your credit card payment, to facilitate your viewing of our web site, and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and website usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. If requested by you, site owner uses your e-mail address to send periodic e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mail to you about services and products offered by us, You will not receive any e-mail from us unless you have requested it and can indicate at any time that you do not wish to receive e-mail information from us. We do not provide your e-mail to third parties without your express consent.

**How secure is my information?**  
Site owner takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you. We provide you with a secure payment gateway to submit your billing information when you join the membership portion of our website. We maintain your personally identifiable information in a secure operating environment, including storing such information behind a firewall.

**Links To Third Party Sites**  
This site may contain links to sites which are controlled by third parties. Those linked sites are not under the control of site owner and site owner is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a link site. Site owner is providing those links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by site owner of any linked site. Pursuant to the terms of service, licensee understands that the act of clicking on a third party link is the act of leaving this site. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third party websites. You are encouraged to read and understand the privacy policy of every website you visit.

**Comment and Public Feedback**  
Please be aware that any public postings or comments made by members of this site are indeed public and are not under the control of this privacy policy. Do not post any personal information you don’t want to become public information.

**Questions or Concerns?**  
Site owner recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. The security of your personal information is of utmost concern to us. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: webmaster [@] mplstudios.com. Please note that persons under the age of 18 are prohibited from viewing our web site, and site owner does not knowingly collect any personal information from persons under the age of 18. Please also note that site owner is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which it may provide links or the websites of its affiliates or advertisers.
